<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Fursonas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Fursonas</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:50:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 07:50:14 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>GIF<br>
<br>turnable
<br>shifting texture
]]></description><link>untitled.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Untitled.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Untitled 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>untitled-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Untitled 1.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 13:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This is your new vault.<br>Make a note of something, <a data-href="create a link" href="create a link" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">create a link</a>, or try <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="https://help.obsidian.md/Plugins/Importer" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="https://help.obsidian.md/Plugins/Importer" target="_blank">the Importer</a>!<br>When you're ready, delete this note and make the vault your own.<br>comic/stroy with narvo<br>
locktober<br>sharkacuga pokemon card]]></description><link>welcome.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Welcome.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 12:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Draconis]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="right" src="draconis\assets\model-turn.gif" style="width: 300px; max-width: 100%;"> ]]></description><link>draconis\draconis.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Draconis/Draconis.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 13:52:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="draconis\assets\model-turn.gif" length="0" type="image/gif"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="draconis\assets\model-turn.gif"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Skit 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Skit one: Master trying to go to work but Sharkacuga wants attention<br>Sharkacuga clinging onto his leg begging him not to go. Master tries to convince his pet that he has to go, and Sharkacuga threatens to be a brat. Master looks at him with a devilish smile, seeing if he was being serious about the threat.<br>Dragon Prince is heading out the door as he shouted with a loving tone.<br>Dragon Prince: Alrighty i'm off to work now. I should be home by 9:30pm my pet. Make sure you eat your breakfast.”<br>Sharkacuga walks in with a pouty face. He stands in the dining room with his arms crossed with a sad yet annoyed face as he sees his master going to work.<br>Skarkacuga: But Master I want attention. Please stay this time. Just call off work.<br>Dragon Prince was looking at his pet with a face that he understood what he was wanting at the time but spoke in a loving yet stern tone.<br>Dragon Prince: But my pet, I have to head in. I just can;t call off. But I promise you we will have a quiet evening together.<br>Dragon Prince walked over to Skarkacuga and he gently held him close to him while kissing him on the forehead. Then he spoke as he looked into his pet’s eyes.<br>Dragon Prince: We can even rewatch BNA together.<br>But Sharkacuga was still a little bit annoyed in his eyes.<br>Sharkacuga: But master, we can watch it now. Just stay home. I want attention from my beautiful master. Screw your manager and your job.<br>With an annoyed look in his eyes, Sharkacuga backed away just a little bit with his arms still crossed looking at his master. Dragon Prince was starting to show a face of sterness and a smile as he was seeing his pet being a bit stubborn. Now they were standing in front of each other. Dragon Prince was crossing his arms with a gentle yet devilish grin.<br>Dragon Prince: Pet you better not be planning something like you did last time.<br>Sharkacuga was starting to smile that he was planning something. He was just smiling as turned his back to his master and started to speak in a tone that was bratty yet loving.<br>Sharkacuga: Well you ‘bottom’ I can see you’re the one being submissive to your job. Well I guess I’ll be the one in charge in this house and you're going to kneel.<br>Dragon Prince was starting to show a smile that he was interested yet annoyed from being called a ‘bottom’. Sharkacuga was about to speak but Dragon Prince pinned him against the wall as he did a low growl as he gently pulls Sharkacuga collar making him look into his look into his eyes. Sharkacuga was starting to blush red as feels his master gently pulling his collar.<br>Dragon Prince: What was that my pet? Did you call me a bottom?<br>Sharkacuga: Ummmmm yeah. I called you a ‘bottom’. What are you going to do about it?<br>Dragon Prince: Hehehe. Such a cutie when you’re trying to be a brat to me.&nbsp;<br>Sharkacuga: I’m always going to be a brat if you don't give me enough attention master.<br>&nbsp; Now are you going to stay home ‘bottom’?<br>Dragon Prince was starting to do a low yet lustful growl as he was gently pinning Sharkagcua’s arms above his head. Sharkacuga was starting to moan softly as he felt his arms being pinned above his head as he was looking into his eyes. Dragon Prince was smiling devilishly as he had his pet pinned against the wall.<br>Dragon Prince: Hmmmm you naughty dragon. You know what happens when you call me&nbsp; that my pet. Now I think I have to teach you a lesson in manners, my dragon.<br>Sharkacuga: Ahhh master. What are you saying? What do you mean teaching me some&nbsp; manners?<br>Dragon Prince: (One eye glows a lustful red.) Oh I think you know I mean by that my pet&nbsp; hehehehe.<br>Sharkacuga was starting to moan a bit louder as was feeling his master gently biting his neck and grabbing his ass with a gentle yet firm grip.&nbsp; Dragon Prince was smiling; he was hearing his pet moaning from his touch. Sharkacuga was feeling his heart race; he was breathing heavily from his lust. That when Dragon Prince was starting to gently squeeze his bulge, causing him to moan in a tone of resistance yet lustful. Sharkacuga was starting to feel his body was heating up in lustful desire as Dragon Prince was starting to slide his hand into Sharkacuga’s jockstrap.<br>Dragon Prince: Hmmmm. Such a good boy. Moaning for your master, my pet.<br>Sharkacuga: (Starting to growl as he was moaning) Fuck you Dragon.<br>Dragon Prince: (WIth a devilish grin and a low growl as he was gently stroking&nbsp; Sharkacuga’s cock.) mmmmm that. I can do for you my pet if you beg like&nbsp; good boy.<br>Sharkacuga: (Starting to feel his cock getting hard as Dragon Prince was stroking him.&nbsp; He couldn’t help but moan louder as Dragon Prince was gently stroking&nbsp; his cock while gently biting his neck.) Ahhhggg mmmm master.<br>Dragon Prince:]]></description><link>sharkacuga\storys\dragon-prince\skit-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Sharkacuga/Storys/Dragon Prince/Skit 1.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Sharkacuga makes a deal with otisha and otisha pins sharkacuga to the wall (what kind of deal)<br>
render with sharks hands above hes head]]></description><link>sharkacuga\storys\dragon-prince\untitled.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Sharkacuga/Storys/Dragon Prince/Untitled.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:27:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sharkacuga]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Ref sheet.jpg" src="sharkacuga\ref-sheet.jpg">]]></description><link>sharkacuga\sharkacuga.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Sharkacuga/Sharkacuga.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:46:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="sharkacuga\ref-sheet.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="sharkacuga\ref-sheet.jpg"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>